realmealrevolution.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Real Meal Revolution

The Real Meal Revolution shall take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information and for the purpose of this clause, “personal information” shall be defined as detailed in the Freedom of Information Act 2000 (FIA). The FIA may be downloaded from: <http://www.legislation.gov.uk/ukpga/2000/36/pdfs/ukpga_20000036_en.pdf>

  1. **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or purchase any products or services via the realmealrevolution.com and related sub domains (the “Website”). When making a purchase via our the Website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, physical and/or billing address, phone number or credit card information.

  2. **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

_To process requests_

To provide you with access to restricted pages on this Website; and to compile non-personal statistical information about browsing habits, click-patterns and access to the Website. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

_To send periodic emails_

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. The email address you provide for email newsletter will be used to send you company newsletters.

  3. **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you make use of the website. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorised with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. Your credit card details will not be stored on our servers.

  4. **Do we use cookies?**

Yes: Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognise your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to automatically sign you in only if you have checked the “Remember Me” checkbox on the login page. Information detailed above is collected either electronically by using cookies or is provided voluntarily by you. You may determine cookie use independently through your browser settings.

  5. **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Essentially, we shall not disclose personal information from you unless:

  1. You consent thereto in writing;
  2. it is in the public interest to do so;
  3. it is necessary to protect the rights of the Provider; or
  4. if it is required to do so by a court of law.

Whenever you are of the opinion that we have failed to comply with FIA, you may contact us by sending an email to [info@realmealrevolution.com](mailto:info@realmealrevolution.com). We will review your representations made by email and, if within our sole and absolute discretion, take corrective action and in any event within 20 (twenty) days respond to you informing about corrective actions taken, if any.

Despite such undertaking herein, it is possible for Internet-based communications to be intercepted. Without the use of encryption, the Internet is not a secure medium and privacy cannot be ensured. Internet email is vulnerable to interception and forging. We will not be responsible for any damages to you or any third party may suffer as a result of the transmission or confidential or disclosed information that you make to us through the Internet, or that you expressly or implicitly authorise us to make, or for any errors or any changes made to any transmitted information.

To ensure acquaintance with and awareness of the privacy measures and policies provided herein, you are urged to take care to read and understand the underlying privacy clauses incorporated in these terms and conditions.

  6. **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

  7. **Interception and Monitoring**

You agree that your communications on this Website may be intercepted, blocked, read, deleted, disclosed and used, as defined in the Telecommunications Act 1984, by Us or any other competent authority.

  8. **Privacy: casual surfing**

You may visit the Website without providing any personal information. The Website servers will in such instances collect the IP address of your computer, but not the email address or any other distinguishing information. This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent at the Website, pages viewed, etc. The Real Meal Revolution uses this information to determine use of the Website, and to improve Content thereon. The Real Meal Revolution assumes no obligation to protect this information, and may copy, distribute or otherwise use such information without limitation.

  9. **Privacy: Unsolicited Information**

If you post unsolicited content of other information (“Information”) to the Website and does not indicate otherwise you grant to Real Meal Revolution a non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable and fully sub-licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such Information throughout the world in any media. You grant to us the right to use the name that you submit in connection with such Information, if they choose. You warrant that:

  1. You own or otherwise control all of the rights to the Information that You post;
  2. The Information is accurate;
  3. By the supply of the Information to us;
  4. You do not violate this policy and does not infringe the rights of any person or entity; and
  5. You indemnify us for all claims resulting from the receipt by us of the Information You supply to us.

Real Meal Revolution may monitor and edit or remove any Information, where posted to public pages. Real Meal Revolution takes no responsibility, and assumes no liability for any Information posted by you or any third party on your behalf.

  10. **Privacy: Solicited Information you give us**

Real Meal Revolution requires certain personal information necessary to process transactions if you require any of our services. Real Meal Revolution receives and stores all information, including personal information which you enter on the Website or gives to us, in any other way. You may choose not to provide certain personal information, but that may limit the services or products that you may wish to obtain from us. Real Meal Revolution provides our products and services in conjunction with our affiliates and subsidiaries. In this regard and unless specifically restricted by you from the license below, you and when entering into the specific transactions in question expressly grants in writing to us a non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable and fully sub-licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such information throughout the world in any media. Your information that is required by affiliates and subsidiaries to give effect to transactions that you choose to enter into is shared with those entities.

  11. **Privacy: Promotional Information**

Real Meal Revolution aspires to provide first-class service to our customers requiring us to provide information to you about new services or special offers. In each instance, you are provided an opportunity to opt-out of such information circulars.

  12. **Privacy: Business Transfers**

Real Meal Revolution may enter into business arrangements and our customer base is one of the more valued assets. In such an event, customer information will be one of the transferable assets.

  13. **Privacy: Surveys and Statistical Profiles**

Real Meal Revolution understands that efficiency and customer care translates to good service. Real Meal Revolution may periodically conduct online customer care surveys to enable the updating of service standards. When Real Meal Revolution conducts a survey, we must inform you how the information gathered will be used, and provide you with the opportunity to opt-out from such surveys. Real Meal Revolution may choose to use personal information to compile profiles for statistical purposes and may choose to trade with such profiles and statistical data, as long as the profiles or statistical data cannot be linked to any specific data subject, including you, by a third party.

  14. **Privacy: Storage**

Personal information will be stored for as long as it is used and for a period of one year, together with a record of the personal information and the specific purposes it was collected for. Personal information will be destroyed once it has become obsolete (out of date or unusable).

  15. **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

  16. **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at realmealrevolution.com/terms.

  17. **Your Consent**

By using our Website, you consent to our  privacy policy and terms and conditions.

  18. **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
